tell me a little about the big deal of ITC. There is a big deal for Infratis as well.
See, you are already in confidence.
Interses. Please tell me what is going on here. What happened
in the IT show, TCS Info N,
then your Wipro, further Sail Tech and ITM
Maitri. Results of all four have come,
not a single result in any one parameter has met
expectations. At the
most, if it has come as per expectations,
everything is less. But after that, the IT lion is running away.
Why is it running away? So, I will give you
four-five reasons due to which
we have made a boom in the IITs.
First of all, now everyone has this hope that there will be
recovery in America.
Nowadays, no one talks about recession in America.
Whatever the registration a year ago, such stuff will
also come, it will become like that. Now everyone will
say that the recession starts,
after that when will it get better. So, the first thing is that there is
fear of recession and expectations are also being created. People
talk about recovery after three months,
after six months, after one month, it is okay
and the second one is that there will be recovery or else there will be recession. So,
first thing  Because your business
comes from there. Secondly, the expectations from these companies were
over. Will they do something good
and are they expecting a lot of business from America or
not?
From no expectations. Third thing is that in this low
expectation, all the stocks have been bought at reasonable
valuations.
You will
see Kal Tech type at a multiple of 18-20, or at a multiple of 17-18, but
TCS Infosys type at a multiple of 23-25.
Your valuations are not expensive, they have become
reasonable. Now, an interesting thing is visible in the results this time. The
results of every company are bad. Okay,
despite that, there is not a single company which has
reduced the guidance for the whole year. This
quarter of ours is bad, but how will we improve it in the future?
But this time there is a concession
in the tax run of all the companies so far. You see, everyone has come out with a very
common opinion that
we will maintain it for the whole year as we had
thought, even though this quarter is bad. And
why is this? It is important to understand that the
big deals outside, this company is
in definition.  Some believe it to be 50 million,
some believe it to be 100 million, but the
pipeline was very strong with the last deal. So,
one number of the story is that
global companies, American
companies, are in the mood to increase their IT spending
and with great fear. Look today,
they have a 5-year deal of two billion dollars
in artificial littles, but
two billion dollars for 5 years is small, it happens
with anyone. So, first of all, what I am enjoying the most about this big deal is
seeing the pipeline of these big deals. It is just like the
pipeline of a big deal for Mazgaon or Hall.
If you compare it with that, I know that the
visibility of business has been increased in the IT company for the next 3-5 years. They have this
order in their hands. Then what will happen
with the margin, it will be more or less, there is business, right? There should be business,
if there is no business then we will earn. Like, the
executive capacity has been increasing the most with the season
and this is the biggest point due to which
their business will increase for the next three to three-four years.  This entire
pipeline is being formed for this, so look at the strategy of biodies, we had
talked about one or two strokes, if you
ask me about one stock in the last step, which I
like the most, Infosys, Infosys will do well,
Tech Mahindra, in terms of relationship, that is
in the G space, the space is
not going to get any worse now, the entire channel of getting better, you will find
many small stocks, Jeans
R Technology is another great stock which is
in good action, I think its
results will also come, you can focus there,
you will get many stocks ETV
which you like, you
can think of buying slowly, so these are some stocks
which you can keep in your portfolio,
but the entire mood environment has changed for the overall sector,
you should keep it in mind